<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Default on Arjun9124</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/default/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Default on Arjun9124</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-IN</language>
    <copyright>Copyleft © 2025, Arjun 9124.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:49:13 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/default/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Things That Are but Arent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-10-05-things-that-are-but-arent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:49:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025-10-05-things-that-are-but-arent/</guid>
      <description>things that are but aren&amp;rsquo;t:&#xA;Schrodinger&amp;rsquo;s cat fight club Godel&amp;rsquo;s incompleteness theorem </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>35mm - I </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/35mm-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:59:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/35mm-i/</guid>
      <description>&#xD;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/chemicalprocessingtechnolgy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/chemicalprocessingtechnolgy/</guid>
      <description>An entry from my journal, written in a midnight writers unblock initiated by Sarveshwar Dayal Saxena and fueled by Mishima&#xA;कल पेपर है। और कल चंद मिनटों में आ जाएगा।&#xA;पता नहीं कैसे गुज़र गया दिन पूरा। अधनंगा बैठा था अंधेरे में, तो पिछले कमरे की दीवार से धप की आवाज़ आई। मुझे लगा कोई है, तो बड़े दरवाज़े का मुआइना किया। हवा के दबाव में कुछ परिवर्तित सा था। दरवाज़े के क़रीब एक हवा का बहाव था जो नहीं होना चाहिए था। परदों के बीच की दरार से झांका, तो बाहर पौधे हिल रहे थे। हवा चल रही थी। मैंने परदे खोले, जाली खोली। आख़िर दरवाज़े का भिड़ना हवा के दबाव में बदलाव के कारण था।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unregulated</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2024-06-28-unregulated/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:34:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2024-06-28-unregulated/</guid>
      <description>I like to support the untaxed, unregulated part of the economy. I don&amp;rsquo;t haggle with Rikshawalas. They aren&amp;rsquo;t technically unregulated, they are self regulating. They are perfect order within the lack of order. Nobody decided their prices, nobody made their laws. They operate a thin plane above supply and demand. Ethics and regulations when they exist are based on their morality. They have license plates, but who&amp;rsquo;s checking ?! Even when anarchy befalls, banks, governments and their issued tokens become obsolete I bet Rikshawalas would still be roaming on their screeching whining rikshaws, charged with stolen electricity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instagram</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 22:00:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/instagram/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t had an Instagram account for over a year, and even when I had one I rarely used it. Mostly people delete their social media accounts before their examinations, for me this was reversed as I deleted my account after the exams when everyone was remaking their own. Not keeping an Instagram account for me is more of a political statement than a social one. And I would like to illustrate this in the same passive aggressive fashion which seems to be becoming this blog&amp;rsquo;s staple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Youtube Distraction Free</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023-06-24-make-youtube-distraction-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:05:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023-06-24-make-youtube-distraction-free/</guid>
      <description>Over the years, it has become increasingly hard to focus on the web. With websites and serveices now being designed to make you shuttle from one red dot to another, it has become necessary for us users to preserve our integrities as users and to not become consumers. This article will guide you to removing all sorts of distractions from YouTube, a popular video sharing website which houses a library of videos ranging from casual entertainment to perhaps the best lectures in calculus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short Video Format</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/short-video-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:47:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/short-video-format/</guid>
      <description>Against the short video format The short video format is a non consensual, habit forming, freedom infringing video format that destroys the users attention span. It takes away the users right to consent, delivers them trivial information in bite sized bits of novelty along with a hit of hormones.&#xA;The user while viewing this format loose all their freedom of choice, as videos scroll past them automatically without any decision making involved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Site</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023-04-30-new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 17:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023-04-30-new-site/</guid>
      <description>newsite!&#xA;using hugo this time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
